https://www.aabsys.com/privacy-statement/

Insights
What is GIS ?
Privacy Statement
AABSyS.com believes in building trust with our visitors. To earn your trust, we ensure to safeguard your online privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. In our Privacy Policy, we provide you all about collecting and using your information. By visiting this website, you accept the practices mentioned in this Privacy Policy. Our enquiry form requires you to fill in contact information like your name, telephone number and e-mail address. We use this information to contact you and communicate information about the services you require from us. In addition, we may occasionally use this information to update you about our company’s news, products and services. We will respect your specified method of communication, and will not use or disclose your identity, unless required by the law, without expressed or written consent from you. Our website also contains links to other sites. AABSyS IT is not responsible for the content or practices of any of these sites.
AABSyS IT is compliant with the European Union GDPR regulations. Please click to view our GDPR Compliance Statement
What is GIS ?
AABSyS IT Pvt. Ltd.
Plot No.E/54 & E/54/1, Infocity, Chandaka Industrial Estate, Patia Bhubaneswar
- 751024 , Odisha , India
+91 (674) 662 1016
Global Sales Office
AABSyS IT Pvt. Ltd.
Unit no. 3515 & 3516, 5th Floor, Tower 3, B-36, Express Trade Towers, Expressway, Noida Sector 132, Noida – 201 303, India +91 (120) 499 1414
Center of Excellence in Telecom
AABSyS IT Pvt. Ltd.
STPI buildingPlot No.- 860/4562, Near Income Tax Office, Ambapua,
Brahmapur – 760 010, Odisha, India
Privacy Statement | Terms of Use |
Copyright © 2020 AABSyS IT, ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
